justairticket.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy justairticket,

This Privacy Policy covers the information Justairticket.com website ("website", "site", and/or "We") collects from the user(s) ("User(s)" and/or "You). We are liable to collect User(s)' Personal Information whenever the User(s) registers with the Website, accesses the Website or performs any activity on the Website. 

#####  Information Collection and Use

We receive and store information whenever you access our website Justairticket.com that may include your registration details such as username, password, first and last name, telephone number, postal & email addresses, fax number plus other credentials. You may note that we adopt effective security measures to protect password from being exposed or disclosed to anyone including the agency. Add to this, we collect your shipping, billing, credit card number, tax registration, & other information pertaining to your book travel transaction done using the Website. Your transaction details with the other users of the Website. Your usage behaviour, details of the computer system / computer network which you use to access the Website and perform activity on the Website. 

User(s) can access Justairticket.com without providing any personal information, but still there's some information we need so that user(s) can avail various features and services of the website; book travel, ask us a question, better customer support, plus participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes. 

We may periodically collect your personal & non-personal information pertaining to you from various affiliated entities or agency business partners and advertisers as permitted and required under applicable laws. We may utilize this information for transactional emails, sending various promotions and advertising materials to you. 

We may combine any information collected from other fellow users plus tracking technologies. The primary purpose in storing information from you is to provide better experience on our Website. Top

#####  Information Sharing and Disclosure

Justairticket.com (online travel agency) is the premier recipient of all the Personal Information and shall employ reasonable commercial endeavours to prevent unauthorized access, keep data consistency, and ensure confidentiality w.r.t. Personal Information provided by the User(s). We may disclose the User(s)' information to the affiliated entities, business partners and/or other independent third-party sources for the purposes of the services provided; any other marketing related activity undertaken by or on behalf of them. All the Information relevant to User(s) should be used strictly for the purposes of the Website only. 

Justairticket.com may disclose your Personal Information to such extent as the Agency may consider necessary for you to enter into commercial transactions with other user(s) of the Website. Top

#####  Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Justairticket.com preserves the right to release Personal Information of any User(s) by an order under law for the time being in force to enforce and/or comply with the law. In our sole discretion, we may disclose any information to government, law enforcement officials or private parties that can be necessary or appropriate in below cases: 

  * to respond to claims and legal process,
  * to apply terms & conditions to our products & services;
  * to prevent or stop any illegal, fraudulent and/or inappropriate activity, and
  * to protect the property and rights of justairticket.com, our affiliated 

companies/business partners, our customers, or others. 

Justairticket.com may also provide your Personal Data to various tax authorities upon any demand or request from them. We never sell, rent, or otherwise share our user(s)' personal information with third parties without appropriate notice and consent, except as mentioned above. We may share aggregated and non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our business partners. Top

##### Business Transfers

Justairticket.com may also undergo a change of ownership. We preserve the right to sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including User(s)' Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information in connection with a subsequent owner, a merger, sale of assets, acquisition, or reorganization and/or in the event of bankruptcy. If such a sale or transfer occurs, we will ensure that the Personal Information stored on the Website will be used by the transferee in a manner i.e. consistent with this Privacy Policy. Add to this, we also give affected user(s) notice before any personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. Top

##### Email Policies

Justairticket.com may disclose/use your Personal Data for the above mentioned purposes of the Website. As a member or sweepstakes/ promotion entrant, user(s) will receive e-mail updates from us occasionally about our flight specials, contests, new Justairticket.com services plus other noteworthy travel opportunities available on our Site and/or travel service providers and advertisers. Add to this, this Privacy Policy allows you have full control regarding which emails including advertisements, marketing material & other offers you desire to receive. At any time when you're no more interested to receive such communications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions. 

Children's Privacy Policy/ Parental Consent 

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, minors (as defined under the laws of US jurisdiction) are not eligible to access Justairticket.com (website). We endeavour to acquire a parent / legal guardian's consent before collecting, using, and/or disclosing personal information pertaining to children below 13 years of age. We're committed in safeguarding children's personal information submitted on our website. Parents or legal guardians may contact us to review their child's personal information, if any and request to delete that collected data/information. Top

##### Cookies

To provide you with a better experience on our Website, we use "Cookie" technology. The use of cookies is recommended on the Internet. Justairticket.com uses cookies to personalize your experience on the Website, and w.r.t. advertisements in similar way like as other reputable online travel agencies. 

We may use several types of cookies allow user(s) to log-in without entering their e-mail address each (only your password is needed). We may also use such cookies to keep track of user(s) search criteria depending on their earlier browsing session or to send them a "USPs" email (or similar emails - assuming user(s) has not opted-out of receiving such emails) focusing on destinations in which we think you might be interested. A cookie may also be placed by our advertising server with the premier purposes to track the effectiveness of advertising served by Justairticket.com. 

This Privacy Policy ensures that none of such information is provided to any third party, and is used by Justairticket.com solely. 

You can change the options on your web browser or can use certain software programs to control how cookies will be accepted by your browser. However, blocking Justairticket.com's cookies may disable certain features and make it impossible to avail certain services available on the Website. 

Top

##### Link of other Site

Justairticket.com contains links to other websites for user's convenience and information. Please note that when user(s) visit any linked websites, we have no responsibility for the content of linked sites or any use of the linked sites. If you access these third-party sites, you become subject to the linked site's terms of use and privacy policies. They may be able to collect information about you in accordance with their own privacy policies. We encourage user(s) to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies thoroughly and may be materially different from our Privacy Policy. Of course, user(s) are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of their sensitive personal information and financial information. We don't accept any responsibility and/or liability for the privacy practices of linked site(s)/third parties. Top

##### Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, our practices, and/or the features of the Service(s)/Website. Your continued membership with our Service(s)/ Website declares an acceptance of the future-current Privacy Policy. We encourage you to visit this page periodically to review any changes and to understand our current privacy practices. If you feel the proposed change is unacceptable, you may request us to close your account as indicated in Contact Information. Top
